Who told you to run?
I'm running!
If you want to run, go ahead.
But remember my words well.
We're done! I'm running!
I'll take care of it, sir.
You go deal with the campaign.
So you're playing tough with me, huh?
Hey, hey, hey!
Someone put a curse on me.
Go get a monk or shaman
to remove it from me!
Just this one job.
Money from this batch only.
You're set.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not here to ask you.
I'm forcing you.
- You bastard!
- Hey, hey!
Don't mess with my family.
Or I'll kill you, you bastard!
No way.
I know your weakness.
Singh.
Come here.
Talk to me.
Where are you going?
Nowhere, Mom.
Don't think I don't know your knacks.
You're just like your father.
People can make mistakes,
but don't make the same mistake twice.
That's stupidity.
If you're going to do it,
think it through carefully.
If it's good, just do it.
So you won't regret it later.
Yes, Mom.
Your father's.
He hid it.
Keep it in case you need it.
I don't know how to use it.
Go figure it out yourself.
Today's payday.
I'm feeling fresh!
Hey, Anon.
Tell them.
Right now our stuff is
the best quality on the market.
If they want to order more,
we can deliver easily.
But don't mention my name.
Yes, sir.
But,
did we need this many people?
And weapons too.
Like we're going to war.
We're all on the same side.
Just in case.
Don't you know how ruthless
those Pattaya Chinese are?
If they mess around, we'll deal with them.
We'll wait over there.
And you,
I know what you're capable of.
After this job,
it's your turn!
You'll learn not to mess
with someone like me.
You have the wrong idea.
Heavy weapons this time?
Yeah.
Don't tell anyone.
Yeah, and your shop?
When I'm free, I'll stop by.
Yeah, see you.
(Inspector Toone)
What's up, Inspector?
Right now it seems Singh
and Mr. Anon are very close.
From their conversation,
they don't seem like boss and lackey.
They've worked together before.
But most importantly,
right now Mr. Anon
has been in contact with
the number one candidate
from the Meetham Party,
Mr. Rachin Ratchakit.
Who previously had a case
involving drug suspects
but the case was dismissed.
Keep a close watch on them.
These gangs move drugs very fast.
We might even be too late already.
Report anything immediately.
Yes.
Lieutenant.
Inspector.
I've tracked them to the warehouse now.
Okay.
- Greetings.
The delivery is prepared.
Check it out.
(Chinese)
Okay.
It's good quality.
I think it will go smoothly from here.
We trust you.
Okay.
So should I
send it all at once or...
split the delivery.
(Chinese)
All of it.
Mr. Liang has cleared the way
with all the authorities already.
Okay, good.
What does the inspector say?
They're all here.
Looks like a big batch delivery.
But Singh is gone.
Watch closely. Don't do anything yet.
I'm rushing over.
Take photos too.
What are you doing?
Inspector!
Walk out.
Damn it!
I knew it!
Hey, wait.
Let the dogs kill each other first.
You're clever.
(Chinese)
What the hell are you saying?
You shit face!
Gibberish yapping!
Where's Rachine?
Where is he?
They took all the drugs and
my money's there too.
I'm screwed!
These guys are fucking traitors!
He backstabbed you!
Liang probably
has someone else picking up
the goods from him.
You said you dealt with him before.
That he could be trusted.
Well, this is easy for him.
He got both the drugs and the money.
Yeah, I worked with him.
But he still did this!
How am I supposed to explain
this to the boss?
A lifetime of work, all ruined!
I should just run.
You brought all these heavy weapons.
If you knew there'd be
a robbery, why didn't you...
stop them?
The bomb, you can tell where it came from.
And the car, you knew they'd escape.
Why didn't you ambush them?
You think I'm that stupid?
To let Anon replace me?
Drugs this big,
the cops would know.
Big agents would know there's
a big boss behind this.
And this time it's not me.
It's you.
Rachine.
- You're backstabbing me?
- You're backstabbing me!
- Hey!
- Either way, the target's on me.
What do you want me to do?
I need a scapegoat.
Leave behind a couple kilos of evidence.
Some money. The cops get something,
they'll look good on the news.
But you're stupid.
And you dared to use a shaman to curse me.
Good thing I had a good doctor
help me in time.
And now you're using
an amateur kid to trick me?
Wait, wait, wait!
There are undercover cops everywhere!
The detectives have good eyes too.
And you'll have another case on you.
Killing a police officer.
You better prepare yourself.
Long prison sentence for sure, Anon.
You planned all this?
Of course.
Getting smarter, huh?
I'll start by shooting
this cop in the head.
Hey!
Toone!
Go!
Hey!
Are you human or ghost?
What do you want with me?
I hate people like you the most.
Lying,
deceiving,
cheating.
I've met countless people like you.
Oh, and don't think
that the magic I used on you
is gone now.
Mr. Anon.
You're arrested for
distributing Class 1 narcotics.
You have the right to
remain silent or speak.
Your statement may be used
as evidence in court.
You're an undercover cop.
You know I was forced.
Someone like me could never do that.
I was threatened, you saw it.
Actually, you're...
You can be a witness for me.
Mr. Anon.
We need to invite you to
the police station for questioning.
Take him.
- Cuff him.
- Hey! No need!
- No need! I can walk!
- Cuff him!
I said no need!
- Walk.
- Okay, okay!
I'm walking. Don't push!
Walk!
Inspector.
You should go to the hospital first.
This looks serious.
I'll handle the scene.
Okay.
Singh!
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, we'll talk later.
Take care of yourself first.
Your bleeding won't stop.
Hey!
Singh, you run first. Go, go!
Run first!
This case is complicated.
You'll be the only one screwed.
Run!
I'll get you later.
Go!
What a mess. Total chaos.
I see our brothers
They are so afraid of this battle.
Uncertain if they will survive.
If we lose, we'll all die.
Are you afraid of death?
I'm more afraid of not seeing
my parents again.
Mae Bua.
My wife.
Just being able to protect those I love
so they can live in peace.
I'm willing to die.
What about you, brother?
Are you afraid of death?
I died long ago.
I died when
the Burmese killed my wife and child.
You know
why they killed my wife and child?
The villagers and I
requested troops from Ayutthaya.
But the nobles in the capital
never cared about the small village
where I lived.
We were outnumbered.
We...
were abandoned.
To fight alone.
If the country had been united,
my wife and child wouldn't have died.
Do you still have faith?
I heard that
Bang Rachan
didn't get the cannons
they requested from Ayutthaya.
This battle of ours
will be extremely difficult.
I have faith.
Faith and respect in you, brother.
That's why I came to fight with you,
to save our nation.
Even death won't make me regret.
And even if I die,
I'll become a ghost guarding
our home and country,
hunting down the wicked
and corrupt for all eternity.
Brother, the Burmese army is coming.
Wind.
Water.
Fire.
Only missing a person
of earth element.
Stop!
Hey!
Bring it here!
Let go!
What are you doing?
You tell me what you're doing!
Huh?
Cutting your wrist
to kill yourself?
No, I was just testing
if the skin is tough.
What kind of crazy person tests
their own wrist?
Where were you yesterday?
I don't think you've ever seen this.
How do you know I've never seen it?
Or never even owned it before.
This thing is priceless.
Hard for anyone to possess it.
Honestly, I don't really want to
give it away.
After owning it for so long,
It gives me indescribable pleasure.
Hey!
Are you okay, Nam?
The images in my head are so clear.
Should we see a doctor?
You're hugging too tight, I can't breathe!
Let go!
You smell.
Did you shower?
I smell.
Did I shower?
- Yeah.
- Really?
See, do I smell? I showered!
- Let go!
- Shower, huh?
Ow! You're crazy!
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
- Crazy!
- That's enough!
Enough!
They are fucking!
Don't tease them!
But I can't think of it any other way.
Damn, look at them in broad daylight!
Don't they have no shame?
Arresting people randomly,
you can get sued back.
Think being a cop makes you above the law?
There's always someone above.
Sorry, Mr. Anon.
For inviting you
to the police station for questioning.
You arrested me
with no evidence.
They cleared the CCTV.
I was just tricked into being a scapegoat.
When I'm an MP, be ready to get kicked out.
The whole station.
So right now,
take care of me.
Rachine. I'm Rachine.
People in this area know the problems well.
Number one. Rachine, your brother.
- Thank you.
- Brought it especially for you.
Number one.
No one knows the people
better than our own.
Hey!
We've been in this district for long.
It's always being developed.
For continuous progress,
don't forget to vote for the same party.
Meetham Party, number one, Rachine.
- Simplistic...
- and productive!
- Selling well?
- All good!
Number one.
Number one, Mr. Rachine.
Thank you so much!
Brothers, number one!
Damn it!
They even had undercover cops.
You know how much I lost on this batch?
120 million.
Totally broke, damn it!
Need to get a new batch.
Get cash to keep things moving.
Soon the cops will come looking for you.
Will it lead back to us, boss?
They'll come for sure.
Someone like Anon is a rat, damn it!
He brought in a strange motherfucker.
Bullets won't pierce it.
How far has the world gone?
Bastard!
How do we deal with it?
Go get the hitters from Muang Phet.
Let them deal with all of them.
Including that tattooed kid too.
Don't let it lead back to me.
Nam!
Have you seen Toone?
I called but her phone's off.
No.
Where'd he go?
Singh, have you seen Toone?
Haven't seen her.
I'll take the customers to the island.
Joe will come too.
We'll be back this evening.
That bastard didn't do anything.
Then you guys put up
the high banners yourselves.
Let's go!
Where's Singh?
What are you guys doing here?
Why so many?
I asked where Singh is!
So I had to hire someone
with magic to protect me.
Is that it?
If you don't agree, then leave.
Come here!
- Where is he?
- I don't know!
Find him!
Looking for me?
Let go of my friend, you bastard!
Hey, Foon! Get down!
Bastard!
Joe! Nam!
Get in!
Did you see their guns?
Yeah.
Damn, they wrapped them in fabric.
I think they know.
If you get shot,
your relic can't protect you for sure.
Bastards!
What's that sound?
Nam!
Fuck!
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
Daddy, it's me!
Damn it!
Min!
I'm screwed!
Hey!
I told you you had the wrong idea.
Just do what I tell you.
Aren't you scared at all, huh?
You people.
Above the law.
What do you want?
Huh?
Money?
Power?
Women? Drugs? Tell me!
Why do you keep messing with me?
What do you want? Tell me!
One,
you didn't obey me.
Two,
you challenged my authority.
Three,
I just don't like your face.
Damn it!
You don't like my face?
I was at the shop with Joe.
Suddenly customers came in.
I told them the shop wasn't open yet.
Have you seen these customers before?
Never seen them.
I don't know them.
When they arrived,
they fought among themselves.
Shot each other up.
Good thing I survived.
My friend Joe had nothing to do with it.
Let him go.
Foon!
- Auntie!
- How are you?
What about Joe?
He's in...
the holding cell.
Mom!
Can you hear me, Mom?
Get me out, Mom!
I don't want to be in here!
A well-bred person like me
shouldn't be in here, Mom!
Mom, get me out!
On Mother's Day I'll ordain for you!
Officer,
I'm here to bail him out.
Okay.
- Just a moment.
- Get me out! I don't want to be here, Mom!
I don't want them to get up
and bite my neck, Mom!
So you remember now, Nam?
I remember.
My name is Min.
I was Mr. Narong's bodyguard.
Trained to do all the shady work.
Actually, I remembered a while ago.
Just wasn't sure
if it was a dream
or reality.
But you just killed several people.
I've killed more than that.
So what now?
I need that book.
Why do you need the book?
Shouldn't we find a place to hide now?
I don't think we should run.
Because even if we run,
they'll find us.
Those whose magics never lose power
are those who have all four elements:
earth, water, wind, fire
combined in one person.
That person will be eternally strong,
impossible to defeat.
The Satra Sutra book,
whoever possesses it
will be superhuman,
immortal in spirit.
But to open it,
you need the blood of someone
born on the 9th day of the 9th month.
Elements:
Earth,
Water,
Wind,
Fire.
And finally, they found it.
Don't let them get all
earth, water, wind, and fire.
People can be deluded
and intoxicated
by evil,
seeing wrong as right.
People will bow to them.
Evil will reclaim faith
in their wickedness.
And goodness,
doesn't it have anything
for people to have faith in?
Goodness is hard to do.
But if you do good,
goodness will bear fruit in itself
and will create faith
in goodness.
Carried by the wind,
from the Khmer with the wind.
Singh, your son,
was born on the 9th of the 9th month.
His father intended to pass down
this dark magic
through bloodline.
But dark elements outnumber light elements.
Your husband fell into the dark magic arts
and couldn't pull himself out.
- Hey!
- Mom! It's Singh!
What are you doing, Mom?
Who knew you'd come?
If you know you did wrong,
go turn yourself in.
Running now means
running for the rest of your life.
Think carefully.
You're grown up now. Decide for yourself.
As for Foon and Joe, they were bailed out.
Where are you two going to hide?
I'm thinking of discussing
with the monk teacher.
staying at the temple for a night.
Can Nam stay at a temple?
Yes.
We'll see first, Mom.
If we can't stay,
we might go to another province.
Should you go stay at Uncle Pong's
in Lamphun?
Probably not, Mom.
Don't want to bother Uncle Pong
for no reason.
Nam seems off. She looks strange.
Not talkative like before.
Well, let's eat first.
I'm about to make kaprao.
Let's eat, Mom.
I'm hungry.
Who are you?
Who are you looking for?
Looking for your son.
How did you get in?
I didn't let you in.
I'm calling the police.
Go ahead.
All the police in this province can come.
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Come sit and talk.
Come.
Do you know what your son has done?
He's caused a lot of trouble.
Your son.
Where is he?
Your son, huh?
He's not here.
There are three glasses.
One,
two,
and
three.
He went out.
I'm looking for someone.
The first one with the water element,
I found.
The second one,
with the wind element,
I think I'll find soon.
The third one,
earth element.
Is the one
with the most powerful magic.
The one known as the legendary,
demon slaying necromancer.
The third one is interesting.
I'm still finding him.
But today I didn't come to ask for help.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Hm, say that again.
Even if I knew,
I wouldn't tell you.